别这样 老兄
Oh, come on, bro.
当黑人可比当同志难多了
Being a black guy is way harder than being a gay dude.
得了吧你
Aw, come on.
昨晚我穿着件一千二的西服去拦的士
Last night I tried to hail a cab in a $1,200 suit.
那家伙就径直从我面前开过
Dude drove right past me
居然去载一个穿着"谁放屁了?"T恤的白人
and picked up a white guy in a "Who farted?" T-shirt.
哼 你只是拦不到的士
Oh, boo-hoo. You can't get a cab.
而我呢 结不了婚也进不了天堂
I can't get married or into heaven.
你也不想结婚或进天堂
You don't want to do either of those things.
这不重要 总统都是黑人 好吧?
It doesn't matter. Look, the president's a black, right?
准确的说 他是混血(半白半黑)
Technically, he's more of a tie-dye.
随便啦 关键在于 如果他是同志
Whatever. The point is, he would never have gotten elected
就肯定不会当选了
if he was riding in cars with boys.
你们俩真是白痴
You guys are idiots.
我要说的就是 你们一定会很吃惊
Look, all I'm saying is, you'd be surprised.
简和我时刻遭受别人的白眼
Jane and I get dirty looks all the time.
但好的方面是你们的孩子会超级可爱
The upside is your kids are gonna be super hot.
没错 混血简直就是上帝的PS
Yeah, I mean, half-black is God's Photoshop.
最坏的情况也只是
Worst-case scenario,
- 看起来像阿凡达的女主 - 她是蓝色的
- you're looking at the chick from Avatar. - She's blue.
不 我是说那个女演员
No, the actress.
她是波多黎各人吧
I think she's Puerto Rican.
没错 她是
She's Puerto Rican.
恩 我东西都清完了 那...
Well, uh, that's the last of my stuff, so...
恩
Hmm.
那... 我们就此结束了
So... this is it.
我觉得你从婚礼上逃跑的时候就已经结束了
I think it was it when you ran out on your wedding.
我做不到
I can't do this.
天哪 我的天哪
Oh, my God! Oh, God.
牛叉!
Kick-ass!
说的不是时候?
Too soon?
你才知道
Yes.
那 如果我落下什么就打给我
Yeah, so just call me if I left anything or...
你确定待在马科斯那儿好吗?
Are you sure you're gonna be okay at Max's place?
什么? 马科斯那儿好极了
What? Max's place is awesome.
你知道我最喜欢你这儿的哪一点么 马科斯?
You know what I love about your place, Max?
它看起来很恐怖
It has the look of a really scary place,
可是感觉起来更恐怖
but the feel of a really, really scary place.
恩
Yeah.
爱死了那些裸露的电线
Love the exposed wires.
外露的墙面也不错
Yep. Exposed wires are the new exposed brick.
皮蓬在世! 唉
Pippen! Ugh.
好了 兄弟们 我先走了
- All right, boys, I'm out.
你不留下来一起玩玩?
You're not gonna stay and hang out with us?
不行
Ah, no can do.
我和简有个约会
Got date night with the old ball and Jane.
我们准备穿上周末服
We're gonna put on our weekend sweats,
吃点中国菜
eat a messed-up amount of Chinese food,
- 看看"单身汉" - 苍天哪
- and watch The Bachelor.  - Oh, my God.
我刚刚不小心睡着了
I just... I just fell asleep.
你们的计划太可怕了
That sounded so horrible.
对啊 我真讨厌玩着休闲电脑
Yeah, I hate relaxing at my sweet pad
和我性感的老婆来个不戴套的爱爱
and having unprotected sex with my smoking hot wife.
听起来真可怕 对吧?
That's terrible. Ew. Right, guys?
你们俩好好玩 顺便说下 你们公寓里
You two have fun, though, okay? By the way, that's bird poop,
有鸟粪 所以这儿应该有只鸟
in your apartment. So there's a bird in here... mm-hmm.
- 活的鸟 - 我知道
- Alive. - Yeah.
其实"单身汉"挺正统的
You know, The Bachelor's actually pretty legit.
阿莱克斯介绍我看的 那是我们在一起
Alex got me into it. Oh, you know, those are the nights
八年以来 我最怀念的几个夜晚
I'm gonna miss the most after eight years together...
就我们俩坐在一起 什么也不做
Just me and her sitting around, doing nothin'...
互相傻笑
Giggling.
额滴神哪 听着 如果你以后要住我这儿
Oh, God. Okay, look, if we're gonna live here together,
不准再在我面前提到这种事
you can't ever say stuff like that around me.
幸福终点站
第一季  第10集
==深影字幕组==
我老实告诉你们吧 单身真好
I'm telling you guys, I love being on my own.
我跟戴夫在一起太久了
I mean, I've been "Alex and Dave" for so long,
我都忘记了自己是谁 现在我要试着了解自己
I forgot who Alex was, you know? I'm learning so much about her.
- 你了解到什么? - 我喜欢斜条纹床单
- Who is she? - Alex likes sleeping diagonal
和用马克杯喝酒
and drinking white zinny from a mug.
你还真是彻底贯彻
Wow. You're really
"美食 祈祷 恋爱"里的准则啊
"Eat Pray Love"-ing your way through this,
- 挺让人羡慕的 - 我还是没整明白
- and it's very admirable. - I still don't get it.
你们俩到底怎么掰的?
I mean, what happened to you guys?
这还是五个月前拍的甜蜜照呢
This was taken, like, five months ago.
我也想知道啊 简
I wish I knew, Jane.
突然之间 本应浪漫的约会就只是
I mean, all of a sudden, a romantic night was watching tv
穿着运动裤看电视 吃着中国菜
in our sweatpants, eating Chinese food,
相对无言 太压抑了
not talking. It was so depressing.
压抑? 是甜蜜吧 这听上去像
Like depressingly... sweet? Because that sounds like
一对互相深爱的情侣
a couple that loves each other so much,
不再需要努力经营感情了
they don't even have to try anymore.
可是如果不再经营
- Yeah, but if you're not trying anymore,
感情就走向终点了 这叫做爱已逝
the relationship is dying. It's called love drift.
有这种说法?
Is that a thing?
- 我听说是一本书里说的 - 是吗?
- I heard it in a book I heard. - What now?
爱已逝
Love drift.
这也太...
That just sounds...
我貌似得走了
I have to go.
什么? 别啊 等等 我们正玩得开心呢
What? No, no, no. Wait. Come on. We're all hanging out.
- 这是女士之夜 - 没错
- It's ladies' night. - Ladies' night.
来嘛 一起才热闹
Come on. Let's all hang out together.
真的抱歉 我和布拉德今晚有个约会
Yeah, I'm sorry. Brad and I are having a date night,
- 抱歉啦 - 别这样嘛
- so sorry. - What? Don't do this.
- 看来又只剩我俩了 - 是啊
- I guess it's just you and me again. - Yeah.
但我有个绝妙的计划
But I have a great night planned for us.
我想也是 你和戴夫分手后
I bet you do. Since you and Dave broke up,
我们还真是做了许多有趣的事啊
you've been planning so many amazing adventures lately.
是你逼我来毕业舞会的
You made me go to prom.
这下你开心了 妈妈?
Are you happy now, mom?
太棒了
Ugh. Yes.
不如我们就呆在家看"单身汉"如何?
Why don't we stay home and just watch "The Bachelor"?
我报了一个超棒的烹饪课程
I signed us up for an awesome cooking class.
真是 太好了
Great. Cool.
周五晚上 两个单身女郎
Two single ladies out on a Friday night,
切切炒炒 打打扫扫
just chopping stuff and cracking things,
真有趣
whisking. Yay! Ugh.
宝贝 简 我回来了!
Janie, I'm home!
宝贝 简! 你又没停好车
Janie! You parked weird again.
我不是教了你怎么发短信和停车吗?
I told you about texting and parking.
哼 哼
Huh! Huh!
亲爱的 你能帮我拿下周末服吗?
Hey, babe, can you grab my weekend sweats?
我一整天没吃东西 煎个蛋先
I didn't eat all day. Gotta get my egg roll on.
你懂我 宝贝
You know how we do, boo. Ha ha!
# 吃个煎蛋先 #
eat some egg rolls
- 你怎么没穿居家服? - 我们出去吃
- Why aren't you in your soft pants?  - Let's go out.
虾米? 我才不要
What? No.
这周工作了八十小时 我们还是
I worked 80 hours this week, you know, let's focus...
中餐 "单身汉" 运动服 吧 快去换
Chinese food, "Bachelor," sweatpants, go. Come on.
- 等等 你这是干嘛? - 享受生活
- Oh, whoa. Wait. What are you doing? - Living. Okay, you focus...
- 放轻松 去吃个大餐 - 等等
- Slacks, fancy dinner, now. - Wait. Whoa. Hold on.
我犯了什么事么?
Wait. Wait. Am I in trouble or something?
你要知道 光看一个人的历史浏览记录
'Cause, you know, looking at someone's search history
是没办法完全了解他的上网喜好的
isn't always a reliable indicator of their web habits.
毕竟 怎么说来着
I mean, a small typo on the word "canal,"
差之毫厘失之千里啊
and you're in a whole different family of sites.
我明白
I know. The same thing happened to me
我曾经有过这样的教训
when I searched for a pair of black crocs.
你说什么?
Sorry?
你没做错什么 只是我觉得
Okay, you're not in trouble. I just feel like
我们最近有点欠缺沟通 仅此而已
we haven't been connecting lately, that's all.
我们今早还做了两次呢
We connected twice this morning.
你还嫌不够吗?
I mean, what more do you want from me, woman?
- 我又没吃伟哥 - 我不是说这个
- I am just a human man. - I'm not talking about sex.
我是说心灵上的沟通
I'm talking about sharing,
从内心散发出来的 那种浪漫的...
about being spontaneous and romantic and...
我们就去第一次约会的那间餐厅好吗?
Let's go to that place where we had our first date. Okay?
那好吧 我快饿死了
Okay. I'm so hungry.
那是我的房间
That'll be my room.
这是你的
This is your room.
你对房间的定义还真是宽泛啊 马科斯
Playing pretty fast and loose with the term "room," Max.
- 床单接着 - 这是通用床单
- Sheets. - These are both fitted.
你不会一直都这样吧 老兄?
Is this how it's gonna be the whole time, bro?
我错了 只是我以前跟阿莱克斯一起住
I'm sorry. I'm just used to living with Alex.
我们有一套规则
We had things a certain way.
你得忘了以前那些
You have to stop focusing on the stuff you had
看看现在这些超酷的新东西
and start focusing on all the cool new stuff you have.
看 那些椅子可是木桶做的啊
I mean, those chairs are made of out barrels.
让我们拥抱新生 吃点披萨
I know. Now let's embrace the change, grab some slices of pizza,
下些阴森林的电影
down these M-light Shyamalans, and go out and celebrate
出去庆祝一下重来的单身吧
your new found singledom.
你说的太对了 对吧? 太对了
You're right. You know what? You are right!
- 当然了 - 我现在就出去
- I know. I know... - I'm gonna go out tonight,
不醉不归
and I'm gonna get absolutely blackout drunk.
- 没错 现在就去 - 也许我会有个艳遇
- Yes. Let's do it! - Maybe I'll meet somebody,
然后带她回来这儿
you know, I could bring her back here,
也许还能说服她在你睡的这个脏兮兮的被子上
somehow convince her to have sex with me on this soiled futon
- 跟我亲热亲热 - 没问题 女孩们就爱
- while you sleep nearby. - Sure. I mean, chicks love
睡在地上的小胖男 让她们回想起毕业舞会
a chubby guy sleeping on the floor... reminds them of prom. Yeah.
几个月后... 得了疱疹
A couple months go by, surprise... herpes.
更糟的可能 她怀孕了 还嗑着药
Surprise number two... She's preggos and loves cocaine.
你想错了方向 想点好的
Okay, you're going to a dark place. Let's turn it around.
我们会试着相处一阵子
You know, we try to make it work for a while,
但很快她会跟个
but it's only a matter of time before she runs off
潘多拉乐队的混混私奔
with a roadie from Pantera. Before you know it,
留下我这个单亲爸爸 和斗鸡眼的宝宝米切尔
I'm a single dad, living in this torture-porn warehouse
住在脏乱的小仓库里
with my cross-eyed baby Mitchell.
如果我们要一起养这个孩子
If we're gonna raise this baby together,
我可不喜欢"米切尔"这个名字
I'm not in love with the name "Mitchell."
那好吧 这个好商量
Okay. We can work on that.
太注重食物的人很奇怪
People who care about food too much are weird.
总会有些奇怪的性暗示和食物有联系
There's always some strange sexual connotation to it.
我管你吃到扇贝时啥口感呢
Look, I don't want to hear about the mouth-feel of your scallops.
来啊 这多好玩啊 我俩一起做饭耶
Come on. This is exciting... You and me, cooking.
大家好啊 小妞们
Namaste, bitches.
啪嗒砰!本人是大厨莱斯利 勒费夫尔
Whoa! Bam! My name... Chef Leslie Lefevre.
我们今天要狠狠做饭奥
We are gonna do some intense cooking today.
我希望你们准备好
I want you to be prepared.
跟随歌曲尽情享乐 准备好我们的频道吧
Let's kick up the tunes and prep our stations.
哇奥 真是个傻冒
Wow. What a douche.
嘿 我是约翰
Hey, I'm John.
嘿 我是彭妮
Hey. Penny.
听着 你看上去很棒啊 但是你会上烹饪课
Listen, you seem great, but the fact that you would
这一点 就算是一振了
come to a cooking class is kinda strike one.
我老婆给我报的名
My wife signed me up.
哦 二振 三振出局了
Oh, strike two and three.
我们分手后 她分到了车子
- Once we split up, she got the car,
我分到了烹饪课
I got the cooking classes.
你有个够烂的律师真悲催
It's too bad you have such a terrible lawyer,
因为我是喜欢车的
because I love cars.
老兄 你知道我喜欢斯蒂文 席格什么吗?
Oh, man, you know what I love about Steven Seagal?
所有都喜欢?
Everything?
就没人能想得出
No one would ever even think about
溜冰溜到他婚礼上还偷走了他的未婚妻
rollerblading into his wedding  and stealing his fiance
没门 我看你溜到席格的婚礼上
No way. You Rollerblade into Seagal's wedding,
当你要溜出来的时候 会被海扁一顿的
you're rollerblading out with your own elbow in your ass.
正是 我就应该把那家伙的手腕打折了
Exactly. I totally should've broke that dude's wrist
-当他溜进去的时候 -是啊 你搞砸了
- right when he bladed in. - Yeah, you blew it.
那就是我的问题 我从没像 席格那样
That's my problem, man. I've never been like Seagal.
我总是更像...扎克 布莱夫
I've always been more like... Zach Braff.
是的啊 你知道我在想什么吗?
Exactly. You thinkin' what I'm thinkin'?
"在云端" 这片子给评价的过高了?
"Up in the Air" was overrated?
啥?不 好吧 是的 的确是这样的
What? No. Well, yeah, of course it was.
谁会相信克卢尼将会在那个年龄
Who's gonna believe that Clooney's gonna be alone
孤独终老? 但是 别啊 我想说我们得找到
at that age? But, no, I'm saying we need to find
那个溜冰的小子...把他海扁一顿
the Rollerblade guy... And kick his ass.
我和你在一起的时候能说点现实的吗?
Can I be real with you for a second?
你说
Please.
这真是你想过的最伟大的主意了
That is the greatest idea you've ever had.
-对吧?!-是啊!
- Right?! - Yes!
-我厌倦了做布莱夫式的人了 老兄!-是啊
- I'm sick of being Braff, bro! - Yeah.
-你支持我吧?!- 是 顶啊!
- You with me?! - Yes, I am!
天哪! 我都热血沸腾了
God! I'm pumped up.
-暴风雨将要来临啦!-噢 是 要来啦!
- There's a storm a-comin'! - Oh, yeah, there is!
-他不能接受事实!-是啊 他不能！
- He can't handle the truth! - No, he can't!
但是我不知道他住哪
But I do not know where he lives
或者关于他的任何消息
or anything about him.
而且你不该开车的
And you should not be driving.
我在开车吗?
I'm driving?
我以为你在开车啊
I thought you were driving.
大概要四十五分钟到一个小时了
So it's gonna be 45 to an hour.
得 那我们走吧
Okay, let's roll.
但 等等啊 这个地方很特别
No, but wait. This place is special.
哎呀 我们聊聊吧 这样就会感觉时间飞逝了
Come on. Let's talk. The time'll fly right by.
好吧 行 聊神马?
Okay. Fine. What's up?
额 要不然你
Well, why don't you...
告诉我...你最害怕什么?
tell me... your deepest fear?
我们在饭店等位子的时候聊这个?
While we wait for our table at a restaurant?
哎呀 那我开个头吧 我觉得我最害怕的
Okay, I'll start. I guess my deepest fear
是你先死了
is that you die first,
我们的公寓对我来说变成了"灰色花园"
and our condo goes all "Grey Gardens" on me,
我将在我剩余的数十年中
and I spend the last decade of my life
疗养一条腿上不会痊愈的伤口
nursing a leg wound that won't heal
然后用吃剩的食物喂养流浪猫了
and feeding stray cats from my mouth.
恩 该你说了
Yeah. Your turn.
哇奥 额 好吧 嗯...鲨鱼
Wow. Uh, all right, um... sharks.
啥?哎呀 严肃点
What? No, come on. Seriously.
额 好吧 是幽灵...
Okay, fine. Ghosts...
鲨鱼
of sharks.
-幽灵鲨鱼? -幽灵鲨鱼?不勒个是吧?
- Ghost sharks? - Ghost sharks? Really?
可能有的吧 额...
It could happen. Uh...
我们知道关于这家伙的什么啊?
What do we know about this guy?
他的名是波...
First name's Bo...
他体格强健...喜欢溜冰
He's got a great physique... Loves to Rollerblade...
轮廓分明 诱人的双唇...马科斯!
Chiseled features, kissable lips... Max!
就是像一个传统意义上的帅哥
Just, like, a handsome dude in a classic sense.
哎呀 那些都没... 没啥帮助的
Come on. That is not... That's not helping.
对你来说没帮助 对我的巴掌累积有帮助
Not helping you. It's helping my spank bank.
等下 等等!
Wait. Wait!
阿莱克斯说过他们在工作时候略微调过情
Alex said they "Flirted a little at work."
我敢打赌他在她的店里为她工作过
I'll bet he did some work for her at her work, at her store.
是啊 比如做模特
Yes, like modeling
或者身体上的劳动啊 比如盖房顶
or something physical like roofing,
或者是抱着我过河
or maybe carrying me across a river.
是 所以做荷兰汁的秘诀就是要感性
Yeah, so the secret to a good hollandaise is sensuality...
-哦-还有小茴香
- Oh. - And cumin.
对 我要从这抓点过来 不好意思
Right. I'm just gonna grab this right over here. Excuse me.
-哦 对不起-好的 让我把这个捏碎
- Oh. Sorry. - Okay, let me just pinch it.
用我们的食指把它放好 然后我们
We put it right in with our forefingers, and then we just
把它放回来
put it right back over here.
哦 好的 恩 好 我喜欢把它放到桌子边缘
Oh. Okay. Yeah. Okay, I like it right on the edge of the table.
盐
Salt.
需要多少盐...然后把它弄碎
How much salt is... and grind it.
彭妮 你是对的 这课很挫
Penny, you were right. This is lame.
-我们走吧 -啥?别啊 我玩的很开心呢
- Let's get outta here.  - What? No. I'm having fun.
-不是吧?-他是个叫约翰的建筑师
- What? - He is an architect named John.
那可是顶尖的两个职业之一
That is a top two job
而且是我第三个最喜欢的名字呀
and my third favorite name.
哎呀 你看 遇到一个叫亚当的
And, come on, what are the chances
篮球后卫的几率有多大啊?
that I am gonna meet a point guard named Adam?
哎呀 那我能不能至少加入你们呀?
Well, can I at least join you guys?
恩 听着 听着 我来当你的恋爱指导吧
Mnh. Listen, listen. I'll be your wingman.
不 不 你是有史以来最烂的指导
No. No, you are the worst wingman ever.
好嘞 哎...约翰 这很有趣吧?
Yes. Just... John, this is fun, right?
老实说 我真不该和彭妮出去玩
To be honest, I usually never go out with Penny
因为所有可爱的帅哥都跟她回家而不是我
'cause all the cute guys always go home with her instead of me.
我的意思不是她和很多帅哥回了家
I mean, not that she goes home with a lot of dudes.
-她不淫荡 但是她也没那么规矩啦 -恩哼
- She's not slutty, but she's not a prude either. - Okay.
总之 她对性方面的好奇心还是很健康的
In conclusion, she has a very healthy sexual curiosity.
-你怎么回事?-是谁推介你报这个班的呀?
- What's wrong with you? - So who turned you on to the class?
啊 我老婆 额 是前妻
Uh, my wife. Well, ex-wife.
哇奥 这是我第一次这么说...
Wow. That's the first time I've said that...
-前妻 -真抱歉 你们刚分手吗?
- Ex-wife. - I'm so sorry. Did you just split?
额 是的 大约是一个月前
Well, it was, like,
也算是 很长时间了 恩
a month ago. Like, a long time ago. Mm.
这个是阿莱克斯店的后门
This is the back door to Alex's store.
很快 很简单 超便捷
Real quick, real simple, simple B&E.
哇嚓!老兄 你在搞毛啊?
Whoa! Man, what are you doing?
你觉得我该怎么做 扎克 布莱夫?敲门吗?
What do you want me to do, Zach Braff? Knock?
我有钥匙的呀 老兄
I got the keys, man.
额 那就不是超便捷了
Well, then it's not a B&E.
你的胳膊甚至都够不着
Your arm's not even gonna reach.
不 我能够得着 我胳膊挺壮的...
Yes, it is. I have huge arms...
不 你够不着
No, you don't.
-特别是右手 -你这暴龙的手臂
- Especially the right one. - You got t-Rex arms.
戴夫
Dave.
我啥也没找着
I can't find anything.
所有的尺码都在这了
Are all the sizes out on the floor,
或者阿莱克斯在后面还藏了更多?
or does Alex have any more in the back?
去查查看电脑!
Just go to the computer!
老兄 看看这个
Dude, check it out.
波 班瑟斯基
Bo Bazinski.
那就是我们要找的人 湖畔广告
That's our man. Lakeshore Advertising.
准备好亲我吧 他家的地址在这呢
Get ready to French my mouth. His home address is on there.
我都不知道他住在西部
I didn't realize he lived on western.
我有个住在那边的男友 他是个摩托党
I had a boyfriend who lived there. He's in a biker gang.
你知道的 额 我们不用这么做
You know, uh, we don't have to do this
如果你不想做的话
if you don't want to do it.
就告诉我一件事...
Just tell me one thing...
这种情况下 席格会怎么做?
What would Seagal do in this situation?
额 我觉得这真是老一套
Well, I think it's pretty cut and dry.
他会乘着老鹰光速飞到 波的家里
He'd fly over to Bo's house on an eagle,
从窗口跳进去 撕开他的喉咙
leap through the front window, tear his throat out,
把它当做一个捉梦器
use it as a dream catcher,
然后骑着一只北极熊闪人
and then ride away on a polar bear.
再告诉我一件事
Just tell me one more thing...
-你想知道事实吗?-我想知道事实
- Do you want the truth? - I want the truth.
-你不能接受事实! -你定了红色代码吗?
- You can't handle the truth! - Did you order the code red?
你他妈的太对了 我定了!
You're damn right, I did!
你为什么要这么做?
Why is that something that you do?
只是觉得该这么做呗 走吧
It just feels right. Let's go.
我们来玩个游戏吧
Let's play a game.
你觉得我们五年以后是什么样的?
Where do you see us in five years?
这是个游戏吗? 额
Is that a game? Mm-hmm.
我们的食物呢?
Where is our food?
哎呀 回答问题啊 亲爱的
Come on. Answer the question, babe.
好吧 五年计划
All right, 5-year plan.
额 我想想...更漂亮的房子
Uh, let's see... nicer house,
更好的车 有孩子
nicer car, kids,
也许机器人在那时候也是个不错的选项
maybe a robot if that's an option by then.
好啊 菜来了 奥 不勒个是吧!
Okay, here we go. Oh, come on!
他们在我们二十分钟后才到这的
They got here, like, 20 minutes after us.
这完全是因为我们是黑人和金发妞的组合
This is totally 'cause we're black on blonde.
好吧 你完全没把我的话放在心上
Okay, you're not taking this seriously at all.
什么放在心上 啊?
Taking what seriously, huh?
你问的这些荒谬的宇宙问题是在坑爹吧?
This ridiculous "Cosmo" quiz you're walking me through?
我没觉得这很荒谬 我希望我们
I don't think it's ridiculous that I want us to be
永远在一起 而且能葬在一起
together forever and get buried next to each other
也许有棵树会长在我俩的墓中央
and that maybe a tree will grow between our grave
然后两个孩子会在树下拥有他们的初吻
and that two kids will have their first kiss
这难道对你来说也荒谬吗?
under that tree. Does that sound ridiculous to you?
是啊 是荒谬
Yeah, it does.
为什么两个孩子要在墓地里接吻?
Why are the two kids kissing in a graveyard?
我不知道!也许他俩是暮光之城的铁杆粉丝呢
I don't know! Maybe they're really big "Twilight" fans
-或者他们只是相爱了 布拉德!-不要啊!
- or maybe they're just in love, Brad! - No!
我的糖醋鸭子!
My duck confit!
我们真的抱歉 我们真是..
We're sorry. We're so...
对不起
Sorry.
你知道最糟的桥段是什么吗?
And you know what the worst part is?
你不仅仅失去了你的爱人
You're not just losing this person that you've fallen in love with.
你还失去了你最好的朋友 不是吗?
You're losing your best friend, too, right?
太对了 那当然是我最无法接受的失去
Totally. That has been the hardest part for me,
那种感觉就像那个你每晚入睡前都要
for sure. It's like that person that you check in with
看看他是否安好的人
at the end of every night.
你知道的 有时候上帝关了一扇门
You know, sometimes God closes a door
却打开了...他的心
and then he opens... up his heart.
也许我应该给她打电话?
Maybe I should call her.
我是不是该给她打电话?
Should I call her?
我不知道 这种事情没有该做什么不该做什么
I don't know. There's no rules in this situation.
不好意思 我要走了
I'm sorry. I gotta go.
我...不好意思了
Y... I'm sorry.
如果你爱她 你应该让她...管它呢
If you love her, you set her...  Whatever.
干的漂亮，傻蛋
Ugh! Way to go, goose.
准备好了吗?
You ready?
好了
Oh, yeah.
波 班瑟斯基 出来单挑!
Bo Bazinski, prepare to meet your maker!
我要让你血染大河
The river will run red with your blood,
我要把你脊梁骨抽出来当棍子用!
and I will rip your spine out and use it as a loofah!
波 在吗?
Is Bo here?
很久都没有BO得朋友来过了
Bo hasn't had friends over in so long.
我们现在该怎么办?
What do we do now?
他妈妈在这里我们怎么办?
How do we do this with his mom here?
我不管 她最好也看看
It doesn't matter. She better get on board.
我报仇不能等
My vengeance knows no age...
他在这儿 孩子们 玩得开心
Here we are, boys. Have fun.
- 谢谢 B太太 -很高兴见到你
- Thanks, Mrs. B!  - Great meeting you.
恩 再见
Mm-hmm. Bye.
-再见 我可以的 对吗? -当然
- Bye. I can do this, right? - Yes, of course.
现在进去 让我们解决他
Now get in there. Let's finish this.
说得好 兄弟
Sweet line, dude.
如果可以...我们就开始吧!
If it works... Let's do this!
你无法接受真相...
You can't handle the truth...
- 波? -我认识你们吗?
- Bo? - Do I know you guys?
你不记得我了? 恩?
You don't remember me? Huh?
我们是在微博认识的吗?
Are we Facebook friends?
是啊 你说的"微博"是他的婚礼
Oh, if by "Facebook" you mean his wedding
你说的"朋友" 意思正好相反
and by "Friends," you mean "No, the opposite of that word."
-哦天哪 是你 老兄 -对了 老兄
-Oh, good God. It's you, brah. -That's right, brah.
我很长时间来一直想找你谈谈
I've wanted to talk to you for such a long time.
我做了一件很糟糕的是 我真的真的很抱歉
I did a terrible thing to you, and I am so, so sorry.
呃 这可没料到
Uh, wasn't expecting that.
没有
No.
哦 那看上去很好吃 我要拿这个
Oh, that looks great. I just need to grab this baster.
算了吧 他显然还没忘了他老婆
Come on. He was clearly not over his wife.
你应该得到更好的男人
You deserve so much better than that.
再说了 今晚不是为了见男人
Besides, tonight wasn't about meeting guys.
今晚是女人夜 不是吗?
It was ladies' night, right?
嘿 梅莉蒂絲 維埃拉
Hey, Meredith Vieira,
你还能有多少个女人夜?
how many ladies' nights can you have?
过去的一周里 你把我拖去
In the last week, you have dragged me
一次空手道和普拉提班 让我试开了一次威姿
to a karate pilates class, made me test-drive a Yaris,
还带我去看了一次孩子们演的《毛发》
and talked me into seeing a children's production
谢天谢地第二幕开场之前被终止了
of "Hair," which thankfully, got shut down before the second act.
等等 那参观安德鲁 洛伊 韦伯 旧居呢?
Okay, wait. What about the tour of Andrew Lloyd Webber's house?
你喜欢那个
You loved that.
那个是弗兰克 劳埃德 赖特旧居
It was a Frank Lloyd Wright house,
而且我一点都不喜欢
and no, I didn't love it,
你还不停地问导游
'cause you kept asking the tour guide
他在哪间房间里写了 歌剧魅影
which room he wrote "Phantom of the Opera" in.
因为他一直不告诉我（因为不是那个人写的）
'Cause he wouldn't give me an answer.
这不是因为你想和我玩
This is so not about you wanting to hang out with me.
这是因为你无法承受
Okay, this about you not being able to handle the fact
你分手了你很孤独的事实 这没什么
that you're alone since your breakup, and that's fine,
但是麻烦你承认这一点以及不要再拖我去那些
but please just admit it and stop dragging me along
可怕的活动了 我们呆在家里
on these terrible activities. We should've just stayed home
-看 "单身汉"就好了 -我把这个放回来
-  and watched "The Bachelor." - And to put the baster back...
滚开！
Get out of here!
听着 你说你想谈谈 那就谈谈
Look, you say you wanna talk. Talk to me.
发生了什么?
What's going on?
我只是...我不想像阿莱克斯和戴夫一样
I just... I-I don't want to end up like Alex and Dave, okay,
把彼此看得那么理所应当
and take each other for granted.
哦 宝贝 别这样
Oh, babe, come here.
阿莱克斯和戴夫的问题不是因为
Alex and Dave's problems had nothing to do
留还是走
with staying in or going out.
关键不是你在哪里 而是你和谁在一起
It's not about where you are. It's who you're with.
我们好着呢!
We're good!
对吗?
Right?
我是说 虽然饿死了
I mean, starving,
但很幸福
but good.
我爱你的一切
I love everything about you,
包括你打喷嚏时候那种可怕的表情
even that scary little face you make when you sneeze.
我打喷嚏的时候表情不可怕
I do not make a scary face when I sneeze.
有啦 你是我认识的唯一这样的人
- You do. You're the only person I know...
-真的? -谁打喷嚏睁着眼睛的?
- Oh, really? - who sneezes with their eyes open.
就像...哎楸！
You're like... ah-choo!
哎楸！
Ah-choo!
看 我们不是戴夫和阿莱克斯
Look, we're not Dave and Alex.
我们是布莱妮和简德
We're Brane and Jad.
等下 好 我们先得把你肚子塞饱
Wait. Okay. We need to get food in you right now.
-我们是简德和布莱 -好吧
-We're Jad and bran. -okay.
我以为阿莱克斯是我一生的爱 兄弟
I thought Alex was the love of my life, brah.
结果她认为我就是"那个帮她从直接邮寄广告
Turns out she thought I was just "That guy who helped her
在当地拉生意的人"
with her direct mail campaign to local businesses."
我不知所措了 我觉得就像失去了一切
I don't know, man. I just feel like I lost everything.
我知道这种感觉
I know the feeling, bro.
你能按原计划行事吗 戴夫?
Will you stick to the plan, Dave?
但是阿莱克斯做了选择
But Alex made her choice.
你知道 你得向前走
You know, you gotta move on.
我们都应该
We both do.
一个智者曾经告诉我
A wise man once told me,
"你不能关注于你有的东西
"You can't focus on all the stuff that you had.
而应该专注于你有的有意义的新东西"
You gotta focus on all the cool new stuff that you have."
你说得对 我想也许是我小时候 很小的时候
You're right. You know, I guess it's because my dad left us
我父亲离开了
when... when I was real young.
我一直在找爱 就好像 用来
I've always been searching for love, to, like, fill
填补我内心的空洞...啊！
that dark void that... aah!
你刚才要打我!啊！
Did you just "Hi-yucka" me? Oh!
老兄!打他鼻梁?
Dude! Hi-yucka?
你想做布拉夫 你就做
You can be Braff all you want,
但我一直是 席格
but I'm Seagal all the time, baby.
你最近看见席格了吗?
Have you seen Seagal recently?
他看上去像马里奥 巴塔利
He looks like Mario Batali.
-我手腕好痛 -得了吧 马科斯
- I hurt my wrist so bad! - Come on, Max.
我要吐了 我要吐出来了
I'm gonna throw up. I'm gonna puke.
马科斯 把持好你自己 行不行?
Max, get yourself together, would you?
-哈！-你甚至没打到他
-Hyah! You didn't even hit the guy.
哼! 呀！呜！
Huh! Yah! Ooh!
嗷！嗷！嘿老兄！
Ow! Ow! Hey, man.
停下！停下！
Hey! Abort! Abort!
抱歉！抱歉！我的 呃...
Sorry! Sorry! My, uh...
呃！啊！
Uhh! Aah!
嘿
Hey.
听着...
Listen...
我为我说过的话道歉 我不是故意的
I'm sorry about what I said. I didn't mean it.
你是故意的 但是说得对
Yes, you did, but you were right.
-是吗? -是啊
- I was? - Yeah.
我是把你拖来拖去
I mean, I've been dragging you around,
把你当做戴夫的替代品
treating you like my replacement Dave,
但是十年了 我一直没有孤单过
but I haven't been alone in, like, ten years,
- 我要崩溃了！ - 不是这样 阿莱
- and I'm freaking out! - Come on, Al.
你不孤单好吗? 你有我们
Okay, you're not alone. Okay? You have all of us.
只是...你真的需要选点好活动
It's just... you really gotta edit your activity choices.
-你说的对 -好了?
- You're right. - Okay?
好了
Okay.
虽然 公平地说
Although, in fairness,
威姿这车很划算
that Yaris was a lot of car for the price.
好朋友很难找
Good friends are really hard to find.
他们随时随地都支持你 哪怕你是错的
They gotta be there for you, even when you're wrong.
但同时
But at the same time,
他们不能只告诉你你想听的
they can't just tell you what you wanna hear.
他们还得告诉你
They've also gotta be willing to tell you
你应该知道的
what you need to hear.
这是为什么真爱这么难找
That's the real reason true love's so hard to find.
因为爱的基础是友谊
Because the basis of love is friendship,
而且真正的友谊很难很难找
and friendship is really, really rare.
所以那就是为什么我把我的第二支玫瑰
So that's why I'm giving my second rose
献给我在场最好的朋友
to my best friend on the show so far.
科尼斯塔 G 你能接受我的爱吗?
Krista G., will you accept this rose?
当我和你在一起的时候
When I'm with you,
宝贝 我们在哪儿没关系
babe, it doesn't matter where we are.
晚上过的够呛啊?
Rough night?
不 没事
No, it was all right.
你呢?
You?
我很好 有个很有趣的厨师...
I was all right. There was this really funny chef...
嘿 闭嘴
Hey, zip it.
我是说 桐亚 B要把玫瑰哭湿了
I mean, Tonya B.'s getting hosed out of a rose over here.
哇
Wow.
-我很专心 - 好吧 我希望你意识到
- I'm invested. - Okay, I hope you realize
桐亚 B根本没一直陪着他
that Tonya B. was not even there for him.
她和他一起去了豪华房间
She went to the fantasy suite with him.
-去发生关系 -去做爱
- To have sex with him. - To make love.
两者不一样
It's different.
今天晚上别让我睡着
Don't let me fall asleep tonight.
我觉得我有点脑震荡
I think I have a concussion.
现在那个混蛋从后面进来 但是他有钥匙
Now the perp came in through the back, but he had a key,
所以肯定是内部人员 有可能是你们认识的人
so it was definitely an inside job, probably someone you know.
所以 阿莱克斯 我有问题问题...
So, Alex, I just got one question for you...
你有多了解...呃
How well do you know, uh...
这个人?
This guy?
哈哈！
Yes!
我告诉过你兄弟
I told you, bro.
当一个黑人有多难！啊！ 当着你的面！
It's way harder to be a black dude. Uhh! In your face!
当同性恋很容易！ 你闻到了吗?
Being a gay dude's easy!  You smell that?
呃 种族歧视
Ugh. Racism.